{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:HF.wrd.10.noShow.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948194918222","data":{"timestamp":" 948194918222"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_142749"," gameId":" 0b0f87b3-1466-43ad-9185-a1691bf5e200"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_HF.wrd.10.noShow.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_walimfuata_kukasirike_alimpeleka"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:HF.wrd.10.noShow.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948194924862","data":{"timestamp":" 948194924861"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_142749"," gameId":" 0b0f87b3-1466-43ad-9185-a1691bf5e200"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_HF.wrd.10.noShow.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_ukiangalia_wakatoroka_nikikuokoa"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:HF.wrd.10.noShow.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948194931534","data":{"timestamp":" 948194931534"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_142749"," gameId":" 0b0f87b3-1466-43ad-9185-a1691bf5e200"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_HF.wrd.10.noShow.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_kumfagilia_kuwafukuza_niliyoweka"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:HF.wrd.10.noShow.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948194938176","data":{"timestamp":" 948194938176"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_142749"," gameId":" 0b0f87b3-1466-43ad-9185-a1691bf5e200"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_HF.wrd.10.noShow.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_ningevivaa_kukosolewa_aliofunzwa"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:HF.wrd.10.noShow.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948194944815","data":{"timestamp":" 948194944814"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_142749"," gameId":" 0b0f87b3-1466-43ad-9185-a1691bf5e200"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_HF.wrd.10.noShow.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_aliniwekea_limezimika_unavipenda"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:HF.wrd.10.noShow.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948194952272","data":{"timestamp":" 948194952271"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_142749"," gameId":" 0b0f87b3-1466-43ad-9185-a1691bf5e200"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_HF.wrd.10.noShow.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_aliniwekea_limezimika_unavipenda"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:HF.wrd.10.noShow.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948194958908","data":{"timestamp":" 948194958908"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_142749"," gameId":" 0b0f87b3-1466-43ad-9185-a1691bf5e200"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_HF.wrd.10.noShow.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_amefunikwa_nimeugonga_nilifurahi"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:HF.wrd.10.noShow.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948194965576","data":{"timestamp":" 948194965575"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_142749"," gameId":" 0b0f87b3-1466-43ad-9185-a1691bf5e200"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_HF.wrd.10.noShow.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_lililoitwa_ukishirika_alimwarifu"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:HF.wrd.10.noShow.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948194972221","data":{"timestamp":" 948194972221"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_142749"," gameId":" 0b0f87b3-1466-43ad-9185-a1691bf5e200"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_HF.wrd.10.noShow.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_akimpeleka_kilichooza_tunayovuna"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:HF.wrd.10.noShow.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948194978854","data":{"timestamp":" 948194978854"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_142749"," gameId":" 0b0f87b3-1466-43ad-9185-a1691bf5e200"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_HF.wrd.10.noShow.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_wanakijiji_walitambua_vimepasuka"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:HF.wrd.10.noShow.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948194985488","data":{"timestamp":" 948194985488"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_142749"," gameId":" 0b0f87b3-1466-43ad-9185-a1691bf5e200"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_HF.wrd.10.noShow.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_tutatembea_akionyesha_ameonyesha"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:HF.wrd.10.noShow.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948194997613","data":{"timestamp":" 948194997612"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_142749"," gameId":" 0b0f87b3-1466-43ad-9185-a1691bf5e200"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_HF.wrd.10.noShow.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" o1_tutatembea_akionyesha_ameonyesha"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-10.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948195048807","data":{"timestamp":" 948195048807"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_142749"," gameId":" c50e6833-0ce3-47d0-89ad-243d5565ac46"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-10.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_kuhadithia"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" k"," userResponse":" k"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-10.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948195051379","data":{"timestamp":" 948195051379"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_142749"," gameId":" c50e6833-0ce3-47d0-89ad-243d5565ac46"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-10.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_kuhadithia"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" u"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-10.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948195054682","data":{"timestamp":" 948195054682"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_142749"," gameId":" c50e6833-0ce3-47d0-89ad-243d5565ac46"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-10.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_kuhadithia"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" h"," userResponse":" h"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-10.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948195057830","data":{"timestamp":" 948195057829"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_142749"," gameId":" c50e6833-0ce3-47d0-89ad-243d5565ac46"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-10.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_kuhadithia"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-10.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948195062127","data":{"timestamp":" 948195062127"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_142749"," gameId":" c50e6833-0ce3-47d0-89ad-243d5565ac46"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-10.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_kuhadithia"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" d"," userResponse":" d"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-10.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948195065041","data":{"timestamp":" 948195065041"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_142749"," gameId":" c50e6833-0ce3-47d0-89ad-243d5565ac46"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-10.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_kuhadithia"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-10.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948195068775","data":{"timestamp":" 948195068775"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_142749"," gameId":" c50e6833-0ce3-47d0-89ad-243d5565ac46"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-10.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_kuhadithia"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" t"," userResponse":" t"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-10.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948195072320","data":{"timestamp":" 948195072320"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_142749"," gameId":" c50e6833-0ce3-47d0-89ad-243d5565ac46"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-10.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_kuhadithia"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" h"," userResponse":" h"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-10.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948195075049","data":{"timestamp":" 948195075049"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_142749"," gameId":" c50e6833-0ce3-47d0-89ad-243d5565ac46"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-10.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_kuhadithia"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-10.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948195078031","data":{"timestamp":" 948195078030"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_142749"," gameId":" c50e6833-0ce3-47d0-89ad-243d5565ac46"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-10.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_kuhadithia"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-10.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948195087687","data":{"timestamp":" 948195087687"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_142749"," gameId":" c50e6833-0ce3-47d0-89ad-243d5565ac46"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-10.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_kudhoofika"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" k"," userResponse":" k"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-10.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948195090286","data":{"timestamp":" 948195090286"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_142749"," gameId":" c50e6833-0ce3-47d0-89ad-243d5565ac46"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-10.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_kudhoofika"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" u"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-10.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948195093997","data":{"timestamp":" 948195093997"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_142749"," gameId":" c50e6833-0ce3-47d0-89ad-243d5565ac46"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-10.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_kudhoofika"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" d"," userResponse":" d"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-10.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948195097628","data":{"timestamp":" 948195097628"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_142749"," gameId":" c50e6833-0ce3-47d0-89ad-243d5565ac46"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-10.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_kudhoofika"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" h"," userResponse":" h"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-10.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948195100453","data":{"timestamp":" 948195100453"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_142749"," gameId":" c50e6833-0ce3-47d0-89ad-243d5565ac46"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-10.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_kudhoofika"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" o"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-10.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948195102814","data":{"timestamp":" 948195102814"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_142749"," gameId":" c50e6833-0ce3-47d0-89ad-243d5565ac46"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-10.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_kudhoofika"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" o"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-10.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948195106422","data":{"timestamp":" 948195106422"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_142749"," gameId":" c50e6833-0ce3-47d0-89ad-243d5565ac46"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-10.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_kudhoofika"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" f"," userResponse":" f"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-10.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948195108868","data":{"timestamp":" 948195108868"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_142749"," gameId":" c50e6833-0ce3-47d0-89ad-243d5565ac46"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-10.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_kudhoofika"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-10.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948195112216","data":{"timestamp":" 948195112216"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_142749"," gameId":" c50e6833-0ce3-47d0-89ad-243d5565ac46"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-10.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_kudhoofika"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" k"," userResponse":" k"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-10.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948195114567","data":{"timestamp":" 948195114567"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_142749"," gameId":" c50e6833-0ce3-47d0-89ad-243d5565ac46"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-10.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_kudhoofika"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-10.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948195124153","data":{"timestamp":" 948195124153"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_142749"," gameId":" c50e6833-0ce3-47d0-89ad-243d5565ac46"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-10.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_aliwaambia"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-10.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948195125953","data":{"timestamp":" 948195125953"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_142749"," gameId":" c50e6833-0ce3-47d0-89ad-243d5565ac46"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-10.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_aliwaambia"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" l"," userResponse":" l"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-10.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948195127816","data":{"timestamp":" 948195127816"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_142749"," gameId":" c50e6833-0ce3-47d0-89ad-243d5565ac46"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-10.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_aliwaambia"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-10.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948195131610","data":{"timestamp":" 948195131610"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_142749"," gameId":" c50e6833-0ce3-47d0-89ad-243d5565ac46"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-10.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_aliwaambia"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" w"," userResponse":" w"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-10.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948195134537","data":{"timestamp":" 948195134537"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_142749"," gameId":" c50e6833-0ce3-47d0-89ad-243d5565ac46"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-10.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_aliwaambia"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-10.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948195137036","data":{"timestamp":" 948195137036"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_142749"," gameId":" c50e6833-0ce3-47d0-89ad-243d5565ac46"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-10.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_aliwaambia"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-10.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948195141382","data":{"timestamp":" 948195141382"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_142749"," gameId":" c50e6833-0ce3-47d0-89ad-243d5565ac46"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-10.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_aliwaambia"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-10.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948195144195","data":{"timestamp":" 948195144195"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_142749"," gameId":" c50e6833-0ce3-47d0-89ad-243d5565ac46"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-10.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_aliwaambia"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" b"," userResponse":" b"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-10.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948195146872","data":{"timestamp":" 948195146872"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_142749"," gameId":" c50e6833-0ce3-47d0-89ad-243d5565ac46"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-10.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_aliwaambia"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" l"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-10.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948195153316","data":{"timestamp":" 948195153315"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_142749"," gameId":" c50e6833-0ce3-47d0-89ad-243d5565ac46"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-10.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_aliwaambia"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" l"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-10.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948195161275","data":{"timestamp":" 948195161275"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_142749"," gameId":" c50e6833-0ce3-47d0-89ad-243d5565ac46"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-10.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_aliwaambia"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-10.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948195163939","data":{"timestamp":" 948195163939"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_142749"," gameId":" c50e6833-0ce3-47d0-89ad-243d5565ac46"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-10.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_aliwaambia"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-10.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948195188453","data":{"timestamp":" 948195188453"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_142749"," gameId":" c50e6833-0ce3-47d0-89ad-243d5565ac46"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-10.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_aliamrisha"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-10.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948195190408","data":{"timestamp":" 948195190408"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_142749"," gameId":" c50e6833-0ce3-47d0-89ad-243d5565ac46"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-10.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_aliamrisha"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" l"," userResponse":" l"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-10.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948195192865","data":{"timestamp":" 948195192864"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_142749"," gameId":" c50e6833-0ce3-47d0-89ad-243d5565ac46"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-10.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_aliamrisha"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-10.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948195196005","data":{"timestamp":" 948195196005"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_142749"," gameId":" c50e6833-0ce3-47d0-89ad-243d5565ac46"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-10.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_aliamrisha"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-10.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948195199923","data":{"timestamp":" 948195199923"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_142749"," gameId":" c50e6833-0ce3-47d0-89ad-243d5565ac46"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-10.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_aliamrisha"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-10.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948195203302","data":{"timestamp":" 948195203302"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_142749"," gameId":" c50e6833-0ce3-47d0-89ad-243d5565ac46"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-10.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_aliamrisha"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" r"," userResponse":" r"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-10.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948195206145","data":{"timestamp":" 948195206144"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_142749"," gameId":" c50e6833-0ce3-47d0-89ad-243d5565ac46"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-10.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_aliamrisha"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" l"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-10.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948195212206","data":{"timestamp":" 948195212206"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_142749"," gameId":" c50e6833-0ce3-47d0-89ad-243d5565ac46"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-10.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_aliamrisha"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-10.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948195215241","data":{"timestamp":" 948195215241"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_142749"," gameId":" c50e6833-0ce3-47d0-89ad-243d5565ac46"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-10.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_aliamrisha"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" s"," userResponse":" s"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-10.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948195221866","data":{"timestamp":" 948195221866"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_142749"," gameId":" c50e6833-0ce3-47d0-89ad-243d5565ac46"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-10.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_aliamrisha"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" s"," userResponse":" s"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-10.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948195229889","data":{"timestamp":" 948195229888"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_142749"," gameId":" c50e6833-0ce3-47d0-89ad-243d5565ac46"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-10.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_aliamrisha"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" h"," userResponse":" h"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-10.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948195232600","data":{"timestamp":" 948195232600"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_142749"," gameId":" c50e6833-0ce3-47d0-89ad-243d5565ac46"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-10.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_aliamrisha"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-10.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948195235946","data":{"timestamp":" 948195235946"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_142749"," gameId":" c50e6833-0ce3-47d0-89ad-243d5565ac46"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-10.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_aliamrisha"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" s"," userResponse":" s"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-10.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948195243823","data":{"timestamp":" 948195243823"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_142749"," gameId":" c50e6833-0ce3-47d0-89ad-243d5565ac46"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-10.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_aliamrisha"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" s"," userResponse":" s"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-10.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948195268484","data":{"timestamp":" 948195268483"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_142749"," gameId":" c50e6833-0ce3-47d0-89ad-243d5565ac46"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-10.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_nilimsikia"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" n"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-10.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948195271367","data":{"timestamp":" 948195271367"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_142749"," gameId":" c50e6833-0ce3-47d0-89ad-243d5565ac46"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-10.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_nilimsikia"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-10.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948195273991","data":{"timestamp":" 948195273991"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_142749"," gameId":" c50e6833-0ce3-47d0-89ad-243d5565ac46"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-10.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_nilimsikia"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" l"," userResponse":" l"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-10.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948195276779","data":{"timestamp":" 948195276779"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_142749"," gameId":" c50e6833-0ce3-47d0-89ad-243d5565ac46"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-10.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_nilimsikia"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" l"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-10.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948195282757","data":{"timestamp":" 948195282757"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_142749"," gameId":" c50e6833-0ce3-47d0-89ad-243d5565ac46"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-10.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_nilimsikia"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-10.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948195286572","data":{"timestamp":" 948195286572"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_142749"," gameId":" c50e6833-0ce3-47d0-89ad-243d5565ac46"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-10.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_nilimsikia"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-10.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948195289042","data":{"timestamp":" 948195289042"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_142749"," gameId":" c50e6833-0ce3-47d0-89ad-243d5565ac46"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-10.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_nilimsikia"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" s"," userResponse":" s"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-10.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948195291590","data":{"timestamp":" 948195291589"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_142749"," gameId":" c50e6833-0ce3-47d0-89ad-243d5565ac46"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-10.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_nilimsikia"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-10.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948195294537","data":{"timestamp":" 948195294537"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_142749"," gameId":" c50e6833-0ce3-47d0-89ad-243d5565ac46"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-10.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_nilimsikia"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" k"," userResponse":" k"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-10.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948195296911","data":{"timestamp":" 948195296911"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_142749"," gameId":" c50e6833-0ce3-47d0-89ad-243d5565ac46"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-10.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_nilimsikia"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-10.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948195299056","data":{"timestamp":" 948195299056"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_142749"," gameId":" c50e6833-0ce3-47d0-89ad-243d5565ac46"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-10.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_nilimsikia"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-10.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948195325759","data":{"timestamp":" 948195325759"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_142749"," gameId":" c50e6833-0ce3-47d0-89ad-243d5565ac46"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-10.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_hawakuweza"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" h"," userResponse":" h"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-10.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948195328397","data":{"timestamp":" 948195328396"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_142749"," gameId":" c50e6833-0ce3-47d0-89ad-243d5565ac46"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-10.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_hawakuweza"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-10.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948195331001","data":{"timestamp":" 948195331001"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_142749"," gameId":" c50e6833-0ce3-47d0-89ad-243d5565ac46"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-10.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_hawakuweza"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" w"," userResponse":" w"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-10.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948195333098","data":{"timestamp":" 948195333097"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_142749"," gameId":" c50e6833-0ce3-47d0-89ad-243d5565ac46"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-10.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_hawakuweza"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-10.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948195336798","data":{"timestamp":" 948195336798"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_142749"," gameId":" c50e6833-0ce3-47d0-89ad-243d5565ac46"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-10.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_hawakuweza"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" k"," userResponse":" k"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-10.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948195339050","data":{"timestamp":" 948195339050"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_142749"," gameId":" c50e6833-0ce3-47d0-89ad-243d5565ac46"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-10.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_hawakuweza"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" u"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-10.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948195342888","data":{"timestamp":" 948195342888"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_142749"," gameId":" c50e6833-0ce3-47d0-89ad-243d5565ac46"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-10.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_hawakuweza"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" w"," userResponse":" w"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-10.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948195345548","data":{"timestamp":" 948195345548"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_142749"," gameId":" c50e6833-0ce3-47d0-89ad-243d5565ac46"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-10.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_hawakuweza"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" e"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-10.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948195349042","data":{"timestamp":" 948195349042"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_142749"," gameId":" c50e6833-0ce3-47d0-89ad-243d5565ac46"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-10.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_hawakuweza"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" z"," userResponse":" z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-10.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948195351803","data":{"timestamp":" 948195351802"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_142749"," gameId":" c50e6833-0ce3-47d0-89ad-243d5565ac46"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-10.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_hawakuweza"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-10.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948195362352","data":{"timestamp":" 948195362352"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_142749"," gameId":" c50e6833-0ce3-47d0-89ad-243d5565ac46"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-10.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_alimwendea"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-10.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948195364446","data":{"timestamp":" 948195364446"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_142749"," gameId":" c50e6833-0ce3-47d0-89ad-243d5565ac46"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-10.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_alimwendea"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" l"," userResponse":" l"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-10.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948195366626","data":{"timestamp":" 948195366625"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_142749"," gameId":" c50e6833-0ce3-47d0-89ad-243d5565ac46"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-10.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_alimwendea"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-10.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948195370926","data":{"timestamp":" 948195370926"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_142749"," gameId":" c50e6833-0ce3-47d0-89ad-243d5565ac46"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-10.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_alimwendea"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-10.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948195374718","data":{"timestamp":" 948195374718"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_142749"," gameId":" c50e6833-0ce3-47d0-89ad-243d5565ac46"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-10.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_alimwendea"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" w"," userResponse":" w"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-10.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948195376894","data":{"timestamp":" 948195376894"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_142749"," gameId":" c50e6833-0ce3-47d0-89ad-243d5565ac46"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-10.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_alimwendea"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" e"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-10.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948195380203","data":{"timestamp":" 948195380203"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_142749"," gameId":" c50e6833-0ce3-47d0-89ad-243d5565ac46"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-10.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_alimwendea"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" n"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-10.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948195383342","data":{"timestamp":" 948195383342"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_142749"," gameId":" c50e6833-0ce3-47d0-89ad-243d5565ac46"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-10.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_alimwendea"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" d"," userResponse":" d"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-10.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948195386031","data":{"timestamp":" 948195386031"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_142749"," gameId":" c50e6833-0ce3-47d0-89ad-243d5565ac46"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-10.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_alimwendea"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" e"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-10.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948195388275","data":{"timestamp":" 948195388275"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_142749"," gameId":" c50e6833-0ce3-47d0-89ad-243d5565ac46"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-10.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_alimwendea"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-10.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948195398098","data":{"timestamp":" 948195398097"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_142749"," gameId":" c50e6833-0ce3-47d0-89ad-243d5565ac46"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-10.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_aliwauliza"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-10.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948195399665","data":{"timestamp":" 948195399665"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_142749"," gameId":" c50e6833-0ce3-47d0-89ad-243d5565ac46"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-10.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_aliwauliza"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" l"," userResponse":" l"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-10.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948195401229","data":{"timestamp":" 948195401229"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_142749"," gameId":" c50e6833-0ce3-47d0-89ad-243d5565ac46"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-10.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_aliwauliza"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-10.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948195404244","data":{"timestamp":" 948195404244"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_142749"," gameId":" c50e6833-0ce3-47d0-89ad-243d5565ac46"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-10.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_aliwauliza"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" w"," userResponse":" w"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-10.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948195407646","data":{"timestamp":" 948195407646"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_142749"," gameId":" c50e6833-0ce3-47d0-89ad-243d5565ac46"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-10.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_aliwauliza"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-10.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948195409603","data":{"timestamp":" 948195409602"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_142749"," gameId":" c50e6833-0ce3-47d0-89ad-243d5565ac46"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-10.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_aliwauliza"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" u"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-10.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948195412473","data":{"timestamp":" 948195412473"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_142749"," gameId":" c50e6833-0ce3-47d0-89ad-243d5565ac46"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-10.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_aliwauliza"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" l"," userResponse":" l"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-10.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948195414347","data":{"timestamp":" 948195414347"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_142749"," gameId":" c50e6833-0ce3-47d0-89ad-243d5565ac46"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-10.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_aliwauliza"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" l"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-10.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948195421718","data":{"timestamp":" 948195421718"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_142749"," gameId":" c50e6833-0ce3-47d0-89ad-243d5565ac46"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-10.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_aliwauliza"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-10.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948195425475","data":{"timestamp":" 948195425475"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_142749"," gameId":" c50e6833-0ce3-47d0-89ad-243d5565ac46"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-10.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_aliwauliza"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" z"," userResponse":" z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-10.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948195428002","data":{"timestamp":" 948195428002"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_142749"," gameId":" c50e6833-0ce3-47d0-89ad-243d5565ac46"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-10.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_aliwauliza"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-10.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948195452083","data":{"timestamp":" 948195452083"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_142749"," gameId":" c50e6833-0ce3-47d0-89ad-243d5565ac46"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-10.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_wakitembea"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" w"," userResponse":" w"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-10.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948195454214","data":{"timestamp":" 948195454214"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_142749"," gameId":" c50e6833-0ce3-47d0-89ad-243d5565ac46"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-10.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_wakitembea"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-10.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948195457043","data":{"timestamp":" 948195457043"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_142749"," gameId":" c50e6833-0ce3-47d0-89ad-243d5565ac46"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-10.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_wakitembea"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" k"," userResponse":" k"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-10.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948195460954","data":{"timestamp":" 948195460953"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_142749"," gameId":" c50e6833-0ce3-47d0-89ad-243d5565ac46"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-10.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_wakitembea"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-10.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948195464348","data":{"timestamp":" 948195464348"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_142749"," gameId":" c50e6833-0ce3-47d0-89ad-243d5565ac46"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-10.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_wakitembea"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" t"," userResponse":" t"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-10.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948195466499","data":{"timestamp":" 948195466499"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_142749"," gameId":" c50e6833-0ce3-47d0-89ad-243d5565ac46"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-10.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_wakitembea"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" e"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-10.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948195470266","data":{"timestamp":" 948195470266"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_142749"," gameId":" c50e6833-0ce3-47d0-89ad-243d5565ac46"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-10.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_wakitembea"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-10.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948195473269","data":{"timestamp":" 948195473269"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_142749"," gameId":" c50e6833-0ce3-47d0-89ad-243d5565ac46"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-10.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_wakitembea"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" b"," userResponse":" b"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-10.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948195476083","data":{"timestamp":" 948195476083"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_142749"," gameId":" c50e6833-0ce3-47d0-89ad-243d5565ac46"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-10.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_wakitembea"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" e"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-10.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948195478347","data":{"timestamp":" 948195478346"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_142749"," gameId":" c50e6833-0ce3-47d0-89ad-243d5565ac46"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-10.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_wakitembea"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-10.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948195487890","data":{"timestamp":" 948195487890"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_142749"," gameId":" c50e6833-0ce3-47d0-89ad-243d5565ac46"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-10.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_alivyokuwa"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-10.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948195489769","data":{"timestamp":" 948195489769"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_142749"," gameId":" c50e6833-0ce3-47d0-89ad-243d5565ac46"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-10.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_alivyokuwa"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" l"," userResponse":" l"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-10.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948195491594","data":{"timestamp":" 948195491594"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_142749"," gameId":" c50e6833-0ce3-47d0-89ad-243d5565ac46"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-10.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_alivyokuwa"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-10.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948195494904","data":{"timestamp":" 948195494904"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_142749"," gameId":" c50e6833-0ce3-47d0-89ad-243d5565ac46"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-10.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_alivyokuwa"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" v"," userResponse":" v"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-10.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948195498271","data":{"timestamp":" 948195498271"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_142749"," gameId":" c50e6833-0ce3-47d0-89ad-243d5565ac46"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-10.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_alivyokuwa"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" y"," userResponse":" y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-10.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948195501198","data":{"timestamp":" 948195501198"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_142749"," gameId":" c50e6833-0ce3-47d0-89ad-243d5565ac46"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-10.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_alivyokuwa"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" o"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-10.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948195504968","data":{"timestamp":" 948195504968"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_142749"," gameId":" c50e6833-0ce3-47d0-89ad-243d5565ac46"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-10.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_alivyokuwa"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" k"," userResponse":" k"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-10.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948195507663","data":{"timestamp":" 948195507663"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_142749"," gameId":" c50e6833-0ce3-47d0-89ad-243d5565ac46"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-10.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_alivyokuwa"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" u"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-10.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948195510742","data":{"timestamp":" 948195510742"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_142749"," gameId":" c50e6833-0ce3-47d0-89ad-243d5565ac46"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-10.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_alivyokuwa"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" w"," userResponse":" w"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-10.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948195512855","data":{"timestamp":" 948195512855"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_142749"," gameId":" c50e6833-0ce3-47d0-89ad-243d5565ac46"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-10.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_alivyokuwa"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-10.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948195526964","data":{"timestamp":" 948195526963"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_142749"," gameId":" c50e6833-0ce3-47d0-89ad-243d5565ac46"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-10.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" write_alivyokuwa"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.5.med.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948195557378","data":{"timestamp":" 948195557377"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_142749"," gameId":" 990c1213-8341-4b65-ba28-ade1c42f7729"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.5.med.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_m_o"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.5.med.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948195593806","data":{"timestamp":" 948195593806"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_142749"," gameId":" 990c1213-8341-4b65-ba28-ade1c42f7729"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.5.med.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_m_o"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" -"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.5.med.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948195601507","data":{"timestamp":" 948195601506"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_142749"," gameId":" 990c1213-8341-4b65-ba28-ade1c42f7729"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.5.med.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_m_o"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" t"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.5.med.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948195609322","data":{"timestamp":" 948195609322"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_142749"," gameId":" 990c1213-8341-4b65-ba28-ade1c42f7729"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.5.med.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_z_nu"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.5.med.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948195622322","data":{"timestamp":" 948195622321"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_142749"," gameId":" 990c1213-8341-4b65-ba28-ade1c42f7729"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.5.med.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_n_e"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.5.med.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948195638640","data":{"timestamp":" 948195638640"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_142749"," gameId":" 990c1213-8341-4b65-ba28-ade1c42f7729"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.5.med.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_m_izi"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" w"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.5.med.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948195648988","data":{"timestamp":" 948195648988"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_142749"," gameId":" 990c1213-8341-4b65-ba28-ade1c42f7729"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.5.med.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_m_oga"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" b"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.5.med.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948195659869","data":{"timestamp":" 948195659868"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_142749"," gameId":" 990c1213-8341-4b65-ba28-ade1c42f7729"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.5.med.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_e_yi"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.5.med.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948195667794","data":{"timestamp":" 948195667794"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_142749"," gameId":" 990c1213-8341-4b65-ba28-ade1c42f7729"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.5.med.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_p_sa"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.5.med.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948195679448","data":{"timestamp":" 948195679447"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_142749"," gameId":" 990c1213-8341-4b65-ba28-ade1c42f7729"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.5.med.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_p_sa"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.5.med.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948195688701","data":{"timestamp":" 948195688701"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_142749"," gameId":" 990c1213-8341-4b65-ba28-ade1c42f7729"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.5.med.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_o_ota"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" k"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.5.med.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948195697231","data":{"timestamp":" 948195697231"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_142749"," gameId":" 990c1213-8341-4b65-ba28-ade1c42f7729"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.5.med.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_r_ha"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.5.med.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948195705667","data":{"timestamp":" 948195705667"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_142749"," gameId":" 990c1213-8341-4b65-ba28-ade1c42f7729"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.5.med.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_h_mu"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.5.med.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948195719193","data":{"timestamp":" 948195719192"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_142749"," gameId":" 990c1213-8341-4b65-ba28-ade1c42f7729"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.5.med.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" write_h_mu"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.10.lc.rand.stat.noShow.14__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948195738693","data":{"timestamp":" 948195738692"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_142749"," gameId":" 42358e3a-ee9d-4428-b0c4-497f7519763d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.10.lc.rand.stat.noShow.14__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kuwapeleka_aliyemtaka-kuwapeleka-alimwambia"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kuwapeleka"," userResponse":" kuwapeleka"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.10.lc.rand.stat.noShow.14__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948195744767","data":{"timestamp":" 948195744767"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_142749"," gameId":" 42358e3a-ee9d-4428-b0c4-497f7519763d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.10.lc.rand.stat.noShow.14__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_alijificha_aliwaambia-alijificha-nimpendaye"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" alijificha"," userResponse":" aliwaambia"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.10.lc.rand.stat.noShow.14__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948195751494","data":{"timestamp":" 948195751494"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_142749"," gameId":" 42358e3a-ee9d-4428-b0c4-497f7519763d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.10.lc.rand.stat.noShow.14__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_alijificha_aliwaambia-alijificha-nimpendaye"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" alijificha"," userResponse":" alijificha"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.10.lc.rand.stat.noShow.14__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948195763291","data":{"timestamp":" 948195763291"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_142749"," gameId":" 42358e3a-ee9d-4428-b0c4-497f7519763d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.10.lc.rand.stat.noShow.14__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kushangaza_nimpendaye-kuwasaidia-kushangaza"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kushangaza"," userResponse":" kuwasaidia"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.10.lc.rand.stat.noShow.14__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948195767329","data":{"timestamp":" 948195767329"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_142749"," gameId":" 42358e3a-ee9d-4428-b0c4-497f7519763d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.10.lc.rand.stat.noShow.14__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_kushangaza_nimpendaye-kuwasaidia-kushangaza"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.10.lc.rand.stat.noShow.14__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948195780650","data":{"timestamp":" 948195780650"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_142749"," gameId":" f4e5525f-ac96-4ec5-a642-0ee0189a9ce1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.10.lc.rand.stat.noShow.14__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kuwapeleka_aliyemtaka-kuwapeleka-alimwambia"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kuwapeleka"," userResponse":" kuwapeleka"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.10.lc.rand.stat.noShow.14__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948195785978","data":{"timestamp":" 948195785978"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_142749"," gameId":" f4e5525f-ac96-4ec5-a642-0ee0189a9ce1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.10.lc.rand.stat.noShow.14__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_hawakutaka_hawakutaka-pundamilia-alimwambia"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" hawakutaka"," userResponse":" hawakutaka"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.10.lc.rand.stat.noShow.14__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948195793091","data":{"timestamp":" 948195793091"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_142749"," gameId":" f4e5525f-ac96-4ec5-a642-0ee0189a9ce1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.10.lc.rand.stat.noShow.14__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_hakupendwa_kingetokea-hakupendwa-alijiambia"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" hakupendwa"," userResponse":" hakupendwa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.10.lc.rand.stat.noShow.14__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948195824208","data":{"timestamp":" 948195824207"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_142749"," gameId":" f4e5525f-ac96-4ec5-a642-0ee0189a9ce1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.10.lc.rand.stat.noShow.14__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_alijificha_aliwaambia-alijificha-nimpendaye"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" alijificha"," userResponse":" aliwaambia"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.10.lc.rand.stat.noShow.14__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948195833294","data":{"timestamp":" 948195833294"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_142749"," gameId":" f4e5525f-ac96-4ec5-a642-0ee0189a9ce1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.10.lc.rand.stat.noShow.14__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_alijificha_aliwaambia-alijificha-nimpendaye"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" alijificha"," userResponse":" alijificha"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.10.lc.rand.stat.noShow.14__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948195870678","data":{"timestamp":" 948195870678"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_142749"," gameId":" f4e5525f-ac96-4ec5-a642-0ee0189a9ce1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.10.lc.rand.stat.noShow.14__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_alijificha_aliwaambia-alijificha-nimpendaye"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.10.lc.rand.stat.noShow.14__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948195906566","data":{"timestamp":" 948195906566"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_142749"," gameId":" f4e5525f-ac96-4ec5-a642-0ee0189a9ce1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.10.lc.rand.stat.noShow.14__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_alijificha_aliwaambia-alijificha-nimpendaye"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.6.init.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948195946319","data":{"timestamp":" 948195946319"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_142749"," gameId":" a00f7ffc-d66a-4150-8623-b0df93ae9605"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.6.init.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write__a"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.6.init.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948195954833","data":{"timestamp":" 948195954833"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_142749"," gameId":" a00f7ffc-d66a-4150-8623-b0df93ae9605"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.6.init.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write__ama"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.6.init.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948195964548","data":{"timestamp":" 948195964548"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_142749"," gameId":" a00f7ffc-d66a-4150-8623-b0df93ae9605"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.6.init.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write__wito"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.6.init.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948195975793","data":{"timestamp":" 948195975793"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_142749"," gameId":" a00f7ffc-d66a-4150-8623-b0df93ae9605"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.6.init.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write__ngia"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.6.init.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948195985096","data":{"timestamp":" 948195985096"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_142749"," gameId":" a00f7ffc-d66a-4150-8623-b0df93ae9605"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.6.init.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write__i"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.6.init.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948195994504","data":{"timestamp":" 948195994503"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_142749"," gameId":" a00f7ffc-d66a-4150-8623-b0df93ae9605"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.6.init.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write__ale"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" Y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.6.init.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948196006489","data":{"timestamp":" 948196006489"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_142749"," gameId":" a00f7ffc-d66a-4150-8623-b0df93ae9605"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.6.init.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write__umu"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.6.init.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948196013658","data":{"timestamp":" 948196013658"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_142749"," gameId":" a00f7ffc-d66a-4150-8623-b0df93ae9605"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.6.init.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write__umu"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.6.init.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948196021570","data":{"timestamp":" 948196021569"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_142749"," gameId":" a00f7ffc-d66a-4150-8623-b0df93ae9605"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.6.init.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write__umu"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" h"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.6.init.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948196066706","data":{"timestamp":" 948196066706"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_142749"," gameId":" a00f7ffc-d66a-4150-8623-b0df93ae9605"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.6.init.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write__witu"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" R"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.6.init.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948196075720","data":{"timestamp":" 948196075720"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_142749"," gameId":" a00f7ffc-d66a-4150-8623-b0df93ae9605"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.6.init.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write__witu"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.6.init.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948196094432","data":{"timestamp":" 948196094432"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_142749"," gameId":" a00f7ffc-d66a-4150-8623-b0df93ae9605"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.6.init.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write__yigu"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.6.init.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948196108044","data":{"timestamp":" 948196108044"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_142749"," gameId":" a00f7ffc-d66a-4150-8623-b0df93ae9605"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.6.init.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write__dogo"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.6.init.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948196121786","data":{"timestamp":" 948196121786"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_142749"," gameId":" a00f7ffc-d66a-4150-8623-b0df93ae9605"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.6.init.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write__dogo"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.6.init.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948196137395","data":{"timestamp":" 948196137395"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_142749"," gameId":" a00f7ffc-d66a-4150-8623-b0df93ae9605"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.6.init.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write__dogo"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.6.init.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948196150857","data":{"timestamp":" 948196150855"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_142749"," gameId":" a00f7ffc-d66a-4150-8623-b0df93ae9605"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.6.init.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" write__dogo"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.10.lc.rand.stat.noShow.14__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948196178812","data":{"timestamp":" 948196178812"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_142749"," gameId":" 3daeb742-ce0e-4632-ab82-3241dc29902a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.10.lc.rand.stat.noShow.14__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kuwapeleka_aliyemtaka-kuwapeleka-alimwambia"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kuwapeleka"," userResponse":" alimwambia"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.10.lc.rand.stat.noShow.14__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948196186352","data":{"timestamp":" 948196186352"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_142749"," gameId":" 3daeb742-ce0e-4632-ab82-3241dc29902a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.10.lc.rand.stat.noShow.14__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kuwapeleka_aliyemtaka-kuwapeleka-alimwambia"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kuwapeleka"," userResponse":" aliyemtaka"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.10.lc.rand.stat.noShow.14__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948196224246","data":{"timestamp":" 948196224245"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_142749"," gameId":" 3daeb742-ce0e-4632-ab82-3241dc29902a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.10.lc.rand.stat.noShow.14__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kuwapeleka_aliyemtaka-kuwapeleka-alimwambia"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kuwapeleka"," userResponse":" alimwambia"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.10.lc.rand.stat.noShow.14__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948196240500","data":{"timestamp":" 948196240500"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_142749"," gameId":" 3daeb742-ce0e-4632-ab82-3241dc29902a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.10.lc.rand.stat.noShow.14__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_hawakutaka_hawakutaka-pundamilia-alimwambia"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" hawakutaka"," userResponse":" hawakutaka"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.10.lc.rand.stat.noShow.14__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948196246012","data":{"timestamp":" 948196246011"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_142749"," gameId":" 3daeb742-ce0e-4632-ab82-3241dc29902a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.10.lc.rand.stat.noShow.14__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ningependa_ningependa-hawakuweza-nilimsikia"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ningependa"," userResponse":" ningependa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.10.lc.rand.stat.noShow.14__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948196254522","data":{"timestamp":" 948196254522"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_142749"," gameId":" 3daeb742-ce0e-4632-ab82-3241dc29902a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.10.lc.rand.stat.noShow.14__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_hakupendwa_kingetokea-hakupendwa-alijiambia"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" hakupendwa"," userResponse":" hakupendwa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.10.lc.rand.stat.noShow.14__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948196263119","data":{"timestamp":" 948196263119"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_142749"," gameId":" 3daeb742-ce0e-4632-ab82-3241dc29902a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.10.lc.rand.stat.noShow.14__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_aliendelea_usichukuwe-aliposikia-aliendelea"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" aliendelea"," userResponse":" aliendelea"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.10.lc.rand.stat.noShow.14__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948196268664","data":{"timestamp":" 948196268664"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_142749"," gameId":" 3daeb742-ce0e-4632-ab82-3241dc29902a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.10.lc.rand.stat.noShow.14__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kushangaza_nimpendaye-kuwasaidia-kushangaza"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kushangaza"," userResponse":" kuwasaidia"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.10.lc.rand.stat.noShow.14__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948196289777","data":{"timestamp":" 948196289777"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_142749"," gameId":" 3daeb742-ce0e-4632-ab82-3241dc29902a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.10.lc.rand.stat.noShow.14__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kushangaza_nimpendaye-kuwasaidia-kushangaza"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kushangaza"," userResponse":" nimpendaye"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.10.lc.rand.stat.noShow.14__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948196300181","data":{"timestamp":" 948196300180"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_142749"," gameId":" 3daeb742-ce0e-4632-ab82-3241dc29902a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.10.lc.rand.stat.noShow.14__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kushangaza_nimpendaye-kuwasaidia-kushangaza"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kushangaza"," userResponse":" kushangaza"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.10.lc.rand.stat.noShow.14__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948196329876","data":{"timestamp":" 948196329876"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_142749"," gameId":" 3daeb742-ce0e-4632-ab82-3241dc29902a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.10.lc.rand.stat.noShow.14__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_alimuuliza_parachichi-alimuuliza-nirudishie"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" alimuuliza"," userResponse":" parachichi"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.10.lc.rand.stat.noShow.14__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948196343763","data":{"timestamp":" 948196343763"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_142749"," gameId":" 3daeb742-ce0e-4632-ab82-3241dc29902a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.10.lc.rand.stat.noShow.14__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_alimuuliza_parachichi-alimuuliza-nirudishie"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"countingx:1_10__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948196357475","data":{"timestamp":" 948196357475"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_142749"," gameId":" 4b31c053-3a2d-4540-be9b-976a8259c875"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" countingx"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" START"," userResponse":" "," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"end":"end"}]}